Guide to the Solomon Sir Jones Films
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Original films
  - Film 25, 1926-1927, undated; (307 feet) (Box 25 (Original))
    - McIntosh Co. Boys and Girls Club Rally Professor L. W. Presly Co., Agent, Eufaula, OK, 1927 April 2; 00:03:43 - 00:04:33
      Includes footage of basketball game
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. J. E. Price, the Grocer, Eufaula, OK, 1927 April 2; 00:04:34 - 00:05:16
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. L. McNeil, The Masonic Wizard and their Rhode Island Red, Eufaula, OK, 1926 September 28; 00:05:17 - 00:06:19
    - Parade, unidentified, undated; 00:06:20 - 00:09:26
    - Big German gun and American Soldiers' Graves, undated; 00:09:27 - 00:09:51
    - In Jerusalem and home of Mary and Martha, undated; 00:09:52 - 00:10:26
    - Solomon's Temple, Lazerath's Tomb, David's Tomb, undated; 00:10:27 - 00:10:51
    - Elijah's Spring, Rachel and David's tomb and Samaritan Inn, undated; 00:10:52 - 00:11:24
  - Film 26, 1926, 1928, undated; (477 feet) (Box 26 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.0-1.1%, 47 splices, some torn, ripped and pulled perforations, some taped splices, punctured section.
    - Flag waving procession (Juneteenth Celebration), Oklahoma, OK, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:02:46
      Reverend E. W. Perry Oklahoma City Pastor, center with banner
    - Reverend R. D. Wess turning C. P. S. S. Convention to Reverend Bridges at Sander Chapel Church, Reverend S .P. Harrison presiding, OK, 1926 July 24; 00:02:47 - 00:03:47
    - Mr. George Dokes Green Mt. Potato Field, Wybark, OK, 1926 July 27; 00:03:48 - 00:04:34
    - Leonard D. Ingram $10,000 Herd of Aberdeen Angus, Porter, OK, 1926 August 2; 00:04:35 - 00:07:06
    - Attorney Charles Chandler and Professor Moore on Ingram Ranch near Porter, OK, 1926 August 3; 00:07:07 -00:07:20
    - 300 acres of cotton on Ingram Yahola Farm, Porter, OK, 1926 August 4; 00:07:21 - 00:08:25
    - One of their farm tractors, Porter, OK, 1926 August 4; 00:08:26 - 00:08:48
    - River and R.R. running the farm, corn making, Porter, OK, 1926 August 4; 00:08:49 - 00:10:17
    - Residence of Charles Chandler and Wife, 908 Market Street, Muskogee, OK, 1926; 00:10:18 - 00:11:26
    - Residence of Attorney and Mrs. Charles A. Chandler, 808 Market Street, Muskogee, OK, 1926 August 3; 00:11:27 - 00:12:00
    - Residence of Mrs. Manerva Jones, Leonard's Mother, 549 North 9th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1926 August 3; 00:12:01 - 00:12:18
    - Law Offices of Charles Chandler, Scofield Building, Muskogee, OK, 1926 August 3; 00:12:19 - 00:12:30
    - His library and Miss Malvin, private secretary, Muskogee, OK, 1926 May 8; 00:12:31 - 00:13:04
    - Post-season [football] game, CANU (Langston University) vs. Wiley, Langston, OK, undated; 00:13:05 - 00:13:56
    - CANU's first touch down of the game, Langston, OK, undated; 00:13:57 - 00:14:21
    - Fun and frolic between halves, Langston, OK, undated; 00:14:22 - 00:15:24
    - Just part of the crowd, Langston, OK, undated; 00:15:25 - 00:15:40
    - Last year men, Langston, OK, undated; 00:15:41 - 00:16:12
    - Old landmark, Baptist Association, session at 1st Baptist, Dr. S. S. Jones, Mod., Okay, OK, 1928; 00:16:13 - 00:17:31
  - Film 27, 1928, undated; (385 feet) (Box 27 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.3-1.4%, 20 splices, few torn ripped perforations.
    - Funeral of Honorable D. J. Wallace, Okmulgee, OK, 1928 September 16; 00:00:00 - 00:02:10
      Jones appears in this footage
    - Mr. Jessie Brown new $75,000 Funeral Home, 540 E. Easton Phone 7809, Tulsa, OK, 1928 September 16; 00:02:11 - 00:03:24
      Includes Brown Ambulance Service
    - Gibson Station Community Fair, Professor D. F. Hill President, Mr. J. M. Roberson Secretary, "Meet Us In", Gibson Station, OK, 1928 September; 00:03:25 - 00:05:57
    - Cozy Home of Mrs. Queen V. Brown, 408 E. 3rd St., phone 2583 J, Okmulgee, OK, 1928 October 6; 00:05:58 - 00:07:34
    - Missionary Meeting at Close General Baptist Convention, Antioch Church, Muskogee, OK, 1928 October 21; 00:07:35 - 00:10:47
    - People gathering at house, undated; 00:10:48 - 00:14:19
  - Film 28, 1928, undated; (386 feet) (Box 28 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.3-1.55%, 24 splices, few ripped and torn perforations.
    - Cars and trucks on a train due to floods, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:00:32
    - Union Baptist Cadets at State SS and BYPU Convention, Reverend D. C. Cooksey, Tulsa, OK, 1928 August 4; 00:00:33 - 00:01:39
    - Ground Breaking Union Baptist Church by Pastor D. C. Cooksey, Officers and Members, Tulsa, OK, 1928 August 5; 00:01:40 - 00:05:19
      Slate can be seen on the building in one of the shots
    - Madam C. J. Walker's $500,000 new building, Madam Walker and manager, Ransom, IN, 1928 August 20; 00:05:20 - 00:05:22
      No footage, possibly damaged and removed
    - 52nd annual session of the Creek Baptist Association, Dr. E. L. Barber, Mod., Mrs. R. T. Jackson, President, Coweta, OK, 1928 August 24; 00:05:23 - 00:08:42
    - George Dokes sizing, sacking and loading this year's potatoes, Wybark, OK, 1928 Jul 2; 00:08:43 - 00:09:22
    - People in a field, cars and trucks on a train due to floods, footage of floods from train, undated; 00:09:23 - 00:11:02
    - C. C. Pyles International Transcontinental Foot Race from Los Angeles To New York City, 3,423 miles, $25,000 First Place, 1928, 00:11:03 - 00:14:26
  - Film 29, 1927, undated; (272 feet) (Box 29 (Original))
    Shrinkage 0.8-1.4%, 10 splices, few ripped and torn perforations.
    - 48th Annual Sessions of National Baptist Convention, Dr. J. E. Wood, President, Dr. Madison and Dr. Jones, Secretaries, Denver, CO, 1927 September 9; 00:00:00 -00:03:01
    - Madam E. Baul, Tulsa, OK, 1927; 00:03:02 - 00:03:16
    - Hooker Studio, Hooker and Lane Baggage and Transfer, Muskogee, OK, undated; 00:03:17 - 00:03:40
    - Footage of water, gardens, zoo animals, undated; 00:03:41 - 00:06:20
    - Ragsdale Brothers, Funeral Home, Muskogee, OK and funeral service, undated; 00:06:21 00:08:22
    - Sunrise Baptist Association, Reverend H. Fletcher, Mod, Frederick, OK, 1927 August 18; 00:08:23 - 00:10:10
    - Blank, 00:10:11- 00:10:41
    - Footage of photographs and slates, undated; 00:10:42 - 00:11:02
  - Damaged portions removed during conservation and reformatting, undated; 1 (Box Damaged portions)
- Reference copies
  - Reference copies of all films available on five DVDs (Box 1)
- New film prints
  - New film print 1, 2011; 1 (Box 1 (New print))
  - New film print 2, 2011; 1 (Box 2 (New print))
  - New film print 3, 2011; 1 (Box 3 (New print))
  - New film print 4, 2011; 1 (Box 4 (New print))
  - New film print 5, 2011; 1 (Box 5 (New print))
  - New film print 6, 2011; 1 (Box 6 (New print))
  - New film print 7, 2011; 1 (Box 7 (New print))
  - New film print 8, 2011; 1 (Box 8 (New print))
  - New film print 9, 2011; 1 (Box 9 (New print))
  - New film print 10, 2011; 1 (Box 10 (New print))
  - New film print 11, 2011; 1 (Box 11 (New print))
  - New film print 12, 2011; 1 (Box 12 (New print))
  - New film print 13, 2011; 1 (Box 13 (New print))
  - New film print 14, 2011; 1 (Box 14 (New print))
  - New film print 15, 2011; 1 (Box 15 (New print))
  - New film print 16, 2011; 1 (Box 16 (New print))
  - New film print 17, 2011; 1 (Box 17 (New print))
  - New film print 18, 2011; 1 (Box 18 (New print))
  - New film print 19, 2011; 1 (Box 19 (New print))
  - New film print 20, 2011; 1 (Box 20 (New print))
  - New film print 21, 2011; 1 (Box 21 (New print))
  - New film print 22, 2011; 1 (Box 22 (New print))
  - New film print 23, 2011; 1 (Box 23 (New print))
  - New film print 24, 2011; 1 (Box 24 (New print))
  - New film print 25, 2011; 1 (Box 25 (New print))
  - New film print 26, 2011; 1 (Box 26 (New print))
  - New film print 27, 2011; 1 (Box 27 (New print))
  - New film print 28, 2011; 1 (Box 28 (New print))
  - New film print 29, 2011; 1 (Box 29 (New print))
- New film internegatives
  - New film internegative 1, 2011; 1 (Box 1 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 2, 2011; 1 (Box 2 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 3, 2011; 1 (Box 3 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 4, 2011; 1 (Box 4 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 5, 2011; 1 (Box 5 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 6, 2011; 1 (Box 6 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 7, 2011; 1 (Box 7 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 8, 2011; 1 (Box 8 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 9, 2011; 1 (Box 9 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 10, 2011; 1 (Box 10 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 11, 2011; 1 (Box 11 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 12, 2011; 1 (Box 12 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 13, 2011; 1 (Box 13 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 14, 2011; 1 (Box 14 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 15, 2011; 1 (Box 15 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 16, 2011; 1 (Box 16 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 17, 2011; 1 (Box 17 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 18, 2011; 1 (Box 18 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 19, 2011; 1 (Box 19 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 20, 2011; 1 (Box 20 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 21, 2011; 1 (Box 21 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 22, 2011; 1 (Box 22 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 23, 2011; 1 (Box 23 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 24, 2011; 1 (Box 24 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 25, 2011; 1 (Box 25 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 26, 2011; 1 (Box 26 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 27, 2011; 1 (Box 27 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 28, 2011; 1 (Box 28 (New internegative))
  - New film internegative 29, 2011; 1 (Box 29 (New internegative))